<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_label">Google Talk Service</string>
    <string name="perm_label">Send and receive Google Talk instant messages</string>
    <string name="perm_desc">Allows applications to use the Google Talk service to send and receive instant messages. Using this service will incur data usage. Malicious applications may cause excess data usage.</string>
    <string name="perm_data_label">Send data messages</string>
    <string name="perm_data_desc">Allows applications to send data messages to other users with Google accounts. The application can send messages in the background, with or without your explicit consent. Using this service will incur data usage. Malicious applications may cause excess data usage.</string>
    <string name="perm_receive_data_message_label">Receive messages and notifications</string>
    <string name="perm_receive_data_message_desc">Allows applications to receive messages and notifications sent by the application server. Using this service will incur data usage. Malicious applications may cause excess data usage.</string>
    <string name="perm_data_msg_broadcast_label">Broadcast data messages to applications.</string>
    <string name="perm_data_msg_broadcast_desc">Can broadcast data messages received from the internet to applications registered to listen for them.</string>
    <string name="permlab_intentVendingOnly">Send broadcasts to Android Market.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_intentVendingOnly">Can send broadcasts to Android Market requesting application installation and removal.</string>
    <string name="permlab_heartbeat">Send heartbeat to Google Talk server</string>
    <string name="permdesc_heartbeat">Can send a heartbeat packet to the Google Talk server to ensure the health of the connection.</string>
    <string name="group_chat">Group chat: %s</string>
    <string name="default_decline_reason">Sorry, I\'m busy right now.</string>
    <string name="newMessages_label">New chats</string>
    <string name="notify_groupchat_label">Group chat invitation</string>
    <string name="num_unread_chats">%s unread chats</string>
    <string name="notification_format">%s: %s</string>
    <string name="subscription_notify_text">%s wants to be able to chat</string>
    <string name="group_chat_invite_notify_text">You have received a group chat invitation from %s</string>
    <string name="message_too_long">You cannot send messages over 2000 characters in length.</string>
    <string name="conn_auth_error_notify_ticker">Google Talk authentication failed</string>
    <string name="conn_auth_error_notify_title">Google Talk authentication failed</string>
    <string name="conn_auth_error_title">Authentication Error</string>
    <string name="conn_auth_error_message">Google Talk failed to login. If this is a Google Apps account, confirm that Chat service is enabled for this account.</string>
    <string name="conn_auth_error_button_retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="conn_auth_error_button_cancel">Cancel</string>
</resources>