<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">App Advisor</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_mandatory_update_message">There is a mandatory update to this application, would you like to download it now?</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_optional_update_message">There is an update to this application, would you like to download it now?</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_close_button">Close</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_update_dialog_title">Update Avaliable</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_info_message">Here you can find applications recommended by LG, These are specially selected for you. They are useful, worthwhile or fun to use.</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_copyright">Copyright © Service2Media 2010</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_app_name">App Advisor</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_install_update_retry_message">If the update was not successful you can retry the installation by clicking below.</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_retry_button">Retry</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_install_update_retry_title">Update Information</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_download_connectionerror_message">The download has failed due to a connection problem, would you like to retry the download now?</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_download_error_title">Download Error</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_error_no_connection">Connection problem detected, please check your internet connection and restart the application. </string>
    <string name="splashscreen_error_title">Error</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_successfull_update">Update successfully installed.</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_download_dialog_title">Download Manager</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_download_dialog_message_extended">Please wait while update is downloaded…</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_notice_title">Notice</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_noupdate_message">Application is up-to-date!</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_testing_message">Version 1.0.1 FOR TEST PURPOSES ONLY - NOT FOR PRODUCTION USE!</string>
    <string name="menu_browse">Browse</string>
    <string name="menu_history">History</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="adviseinfo_download">Download from Market</string>
    <string name="historylist_current_list">Current List</string>
    <string name="welcomescreen_welcome_text">Welcome to App Advisor. This Application allows you to view lists of android applications which are recommended to you by LG. LG regularly updates these recommendations to give you the best applications that are available on the Google Market, these are specially selected for you. They are useful, worthwhile and fun to use. You can also browse old lists of recommended applications as well as for different countries.</string>
    <string name="welcomescreen_dontshow_text">Do not show this message again</string>
    <string name="welcomescreen_title">Welcome</string>
    <string name="adviselist_default_country_set_text">Default country set to</string>
    <string name="adviselist_choose_default_country">Choose your default country</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_heading_description">Description</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_heading_tos">Terms  Conditions</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_heading_functions">Functions</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_heading_version">Current Version:</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_tos">All applications featured within App Advisor adhere to the Google Market Terms of Service. The downloading of an application could be limited depending on the condition of Android Market (Country, Developer, and etc.)</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_function1">View a current list of up-to-date applications recommended by LG.</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_function2">Browse different recommendations for different countries.</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_function3">View a History of recommendations from earlier points in time.</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_function4">Download &amp; install applications via Google Market directly from App Advisor.</string>
    <string name="helpscreen_text_description">Searching the Google Market for good quality applications can sometimes be tedious. App Advisor makes it easy to install the best applications with minimal effort. LG keep their recommended applications up-to-date, based on popularity and rating. You can also access previous recommendations using the history function off the application. LG also allow access to application recommendations for different countries, so be sure to checkout the “Browse” feature off App Advisor found in the menu. You can also download applications to your phone via Google market directly from App Advisor with no need to search. We hope you enjoy App Advisor.</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_error_connection_problem">Connection problem detected, please check your internet connection and retry.</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_close_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_loading_message">Downloading data from LG... please wait...</string>
    <string name="adviselist_loading_advise_list">Loading advise list...</string>
</resources>